{"data":[{"question":"The Nobel Prize winner, accompanied by her husband and children, are staying in Sweden until after the presentation.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Would you like","b":"come","c":"staying","d":"you're in town","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Staying-> stay","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Neither of the scout leaders know how to trap wild animals or how to prepare them for mounting.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"in a","c":"variety of","d":"lack of","answer":"4","explain":" Correct\n\n- Lack of-> lack","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Those of you who signed up for Dr.Daniel's anthropology class should get their books as soon as possible.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"experiment","b":"solve","c":"those","d":"to solve","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Experiment-> experiments","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Would you like to come and staying with us while you're in town.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"a","b":"fiery globe","c":"a","d":"from","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- A-> an","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Since vitamins are contained in a wide variety of foods, people seldom lack of most of them.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"successful","b":"so poor","c":"has to","d":"as","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Has to-> had to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Psychological experiment indicate that people remember more math problems that they cannot solve than those they are able to solve.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Despite","b":"is used","c":"is still","d":"commonly","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Despite-> although","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Before becoming successful, Charles Kettering, former vice-president of General Motors, was so poor that he has to use the hayloft of a barn as a laboratory.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"beat","b":"as","c":"express","d":"high","answer":"3","explain":" Correct\n\n- Express-> expression","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Despite the metric system is used throughout the world, it is still not commonly used in the United States.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Because","b":"those","c":"no longer","d":"dreaded disease","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Because -> because of","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Some gorillas beat their chests as an express of high spirits.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"shelves","b":"of","c":"ocean floor","d":"closest","answer":"1","explain":" Correct\n\n- Shelves-> shelf","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"Because Walter Reed's efforts and those of the people who worked with him, human beings no longer fear the dreaded disease of yellow fever.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"The","b":"get","c":"to","d":"colds","answer":"2","explain":" Correct\n\n- Get-> gets","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"24","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"}]}